Hello everyone! Welcome to a video with another guest today. Hi! This is Jinx and
we're going to try a lot of new handmade outfits today. So a lot of wet look
outfits and yeah enjoy! Here we go!
10? 11? I don't know.
Okay!
Okay, so there's a lot of outfits.
Yes, I see.
I would say let's start right away and choose your first outfit.
Yes. I think I am in love with this catsuit.
Maybe I try this on.
Catsuit for a start?
Yeah.
go yeah yay it fits yeah it fits perfectly it looks really good thank you yeah that's look
looks very good it's uh yeah it shows the dress and uh curl it with some boots and you just yeah
i take some um yeah matte heels i look great together with the catsuit yeah i like these
lace application for you. Oh, yeah. To match with my bra. Yeah. That's quite cool.
Look who's here again and Nono is staying with me again. Oh, now he dropped it. No.
Yeah. And of course we're bribing her again because that's the only way how to do it with cats.
How to pimp your outfit. You said on the Fofra that you really like these metal belts. Yes,
I think in the combination it looks more special and fits perfectly to the ring.
Yeah, that's true. I think you can add it to like every outfit. It's the same.
It's that kind of thing that makes every outfit better. True. So we know each other from
taking pictures, from modeling. You were taking pictures as well. You can find her as Jinx B.
which on Instagram, Facebook? No, only on Instagram. Okay but I'll link it down below in the description
text. Tell me a bit about yourself. What kind of pictures are you doing and what do you like? Yeah
most of the pictures are latex and rubber outfits but yeah maybe you take a look at the profile.
So this is the first time in a video. Yeah, first time for me and also the first
time in Noir handmade stuff. I saw a lot in the internet but I never tried
the outfits before. So how do you like the catsuit? I think it fits perfectly.
I like the zipper on the crotch
It's so handy!
Yeah it's handy and yeah
Also with little boobs
It looks super perfect and yeah
I think it's very smooth material
But yeah then let's take the next item
So we're not wasting too much time
time because we have a lot to do. Yeah.
What? Yeah I like this dress so much. You do? Yeah really. Looks very cool on you.
I like it too. I think it's a dress. Yeah so I like this neck part really much.
Yeah it has a ring again so good for additional accessories. I like this material very much,
very smooth and yeah a little bit shiny but not too much. That's great. But I think what you're
going on is way more interesting. Yes it's I think it's a little short for me but I mean with the
crotch-tie boots yeah it's for a good yeah with the boots it's uh really nice maybe it's good for
um some bad time stories or stuff like that would you go out in a club wearing this uh maybe not
to be honest because yeah it's it's really short and i think when you move a little bit
it will go upside and then I'm naked.
No problem.
But I think with the chains on it...
It's a belt you just added.
Maybe I would wear this for a private dinner.
Or for photoshooting.
For photoshooting.
It's always a valid reason.
I would wear this for photoshooting.
I have to buy this.
Yeah, because it looks good in pictures.
And we're back with another outfit set.
I have to say I'm not totally, yeah, decor or... I don't like my outfit that much.
I think it's a bodysuit and a skirt and I think that skirt is way cooler.
And I like the bodysuit without the skirt better.
I tried all combined it and I guess I failed. Your outfit better. Yeah I like it very much but yeah I like this
pencil skirt. If you turn around. Yeah it has really nice details on the backside. Yeah the lacing makes it great.
Yeah, it fits very well and I like also the details on the jacket like this
reptile. I don't know what kind of pattern it is. I don't know. But yeah it looks very high fashion.
Yeah I think this is my favorite handmade piece so far from all of this I own.
own. So do you like this outfit or the first outfit better? I think the first outfit...
Yeah I like catsuits very much so... I think you're on the right channel here if you like catsuits.
Yeah. I think I'm going to get rid of the jacket. I wanted to try this jacket and... but not with this
No, I think it's better without.
That's good.
That's nice.
But I love your outfit combination.
I love it together with the heels, the PVC heels and then this frilly see-through summer
dress.
Yeah, maybe for summer, for the hot days but it's also very comfortable and very also
closed up.
So you feel dressed.
dressed. Yeah I feel dressed and very comfortable in this. And you? I don't feel that dressed.
But nice on the back. Yeah it's a one piece and I think the leggings part fits really good.
Yeah it's also a bit summer outfit so I think these two go well together actually.
maybe. So after seeing all the outfits today what's your favorite outfit? I think my favorite outfit is
again the catsuit. Still the catsuit. Yeah the first pick was the best.
Yeah and you? I don't know I really like this combination with the boots. So you want this?
I don't think the boots will fit me.
I also like this one.
And I also like the catsuit.
It's hard.
But I like that Noir Handmade has very different outfits for everyone I think.
I like this outfit also very much because it's so wearable.
Okay, so I hope you had fun.
Yeah, a lot.
Hope you had fun watching this video.
Leave us a comment down below, give us a thumbs up,
follow her on Instagram.
And see you next time.
Bye. Bye.